Ho ,oba, Ho ,obi,
Mama, Ho ,obi, Siune!
Ho ,aji, Seal, Zimbabu, S gegangen,
vos, ent ententes get ridin' Hi there!
Time for this week's M .M .O .S.
stream.
You just saw a promo of
today's featured game.
And this is what last week's
launch day looked like!
Can you guess what everyone's
waiting in line for?
Sword Art Online!
The first person in line said
they camped out for three days.
Hey, but if you're a hardcore
gamer, that's what you do.
On today's episode of the MMO Stream,
we'll be covering the internationally
famous Sword Art Online, a .k .a.
FAO. Up to now,
none of the Nerf Gear
software we've seen has taken
advantage of the
possibilities of the hardware.
Hey, I'm off to practice now.
See you later, okay?
by the inventor of their
gear, Akihiko Gabe.
Heck, this is the VR MMORPG that me and
everyone else have been waiting for.
The beta testers say it's incredible.
I wish I could have gotten one.
The first testing was limited
to only 10,000 copies.
Those fans in line snapped them up, and
online the game sold out in seconds.
Link, start!
Hello, world.
I'm back.
Well, I told him, so it's his deal.
Why don't we form a party?
Well, I don't know, maybe.
Oh, come on. It'll be great.
We can go out and do that bad stuff.
Hey, Froze! Wait up!
What's up?
Woo!
You act like you know
your way around here.
You were in the beta test, weren't you?
Yeah.
Cool.
Today's my first day.
So, could you give me some
tips on the lower floors?
Yeah, I don't know if...
Aw, please, I'm begging you.
Look, my name's Klein.
Good to meet you.
Alright, I'm Kirito.
Right in the nuts.
Kill me now.
Oh, come on, seriously.
You can't feel any pain.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
Sorry, habit.
Remember what I said?
The first move is the most important.
Yeah, that's easy for you to say.
But he won't stand still.
If you do your initial motion right
and activate a sword
skill at the right time,
The system pretty much guarantees
you'll always hit your target.
Initial motion?
Here's an easier way to look at it.
Right after you start your
move, wait for a little bit.
When you feel the skills start
to activate, drive it home.
Drive it home?
Woo!
Yaaah!
Yaaah! Yaaah!
Congratulations.
That was nice.
But that boar's about as weak
as slimes in other games are.
Holy crap, you gotta be kidding.
I thought that thing was a mid-level boss.
Yeah, as if.
Whoa!
Addictive, isn't it?
I'll say.
So these skills, there's a ton of them,
like blacksmithing and stuff, right? Uh-huh.
I heard the game has an
unlimited number of them.
All except for magic, though.
An RPG without magic?
That's a bold decision, man!
So, what do you think?
It's kind of fun to move your
body as you fight, isn't it?
Oh, hells yeah!
You ready to move on?
Yeah, man!
Let's keep going!
When I look around I can't
believe it we're inside
a game bro whoever made
it's a genius this thing's
amazing makes me glad I
was born when I was you
know it's not that big
a deal cut me some slack
it's my first full dive
you never used the nerve
gear before today huh
this is your first time
ever uh-huh as soon as
I got the money together
I rushed out and bought all
the hardware to play SAO
Stood in line and scored one
of the 10,000 hard copies.
Guess you could say I was pretty lucky.
Although, you, sir, were ten times
as lucky getting the beta tested.
Dude, only a thousand
people got the chance.
Yeah, I guess I was lucky.
Hey, mind if I ask how
far you got in the beta?
Two months and I couldn't
get further than Floor 8.
But now I think I can
get there within a month.
Easy.
Sounds to me like you're really into this.
Yeah, you could say that.
During the beta test, SAO was the
only thing on my mind, day and night.
In this world, a single blade can
take you anywhere you want to go.
And even though it's a virtual world,
I feel more alive in here than
I ever did in the real one.
Anyway, you want to go
do some more hunting?
But you know it.
But the thing is, I'm really hungry.
I have to log out.
Too bad the food you eat here only
satisfies your hunger virtually.
Yeah, for reals.
That's why I ordered a pizza for 5.30.
Wow, you're so prepared.
You know it.
Besides, the game can wait
until I get my pizza on.
I guess.
Hey, I was going to go meet up with
some people I know from another game.
I don't know what you're up
to after this, so if, uh,
you know, if you want, you can
friend him and hang with us.
No, it's cool if you don't want to.
No pressure.
I can always introduce you to
him another time or something.
Yeah, sorry.
Thanks anyway.
No way.
I should be doing all the thanking.
Hey, one of these days, I promise
I'll pay you back for all your help.
Virtually, that is.
Yeah, right.
Thanks for everything, man.
Really.
Guess I'll see you around then.
If there's anything else you
want to know, message me.
Sweet!
I'll do that.
Huh?
Where'd the logout button go?
It should be there.
Nope, it's not there.
It should be at the
bottom of the main menu.
See, not there.
You're right, it's not.
Oh well, today's what,
the first day out of beta?
There's bound to be some bugs.
I bet the server people
are freaking out right now.
You will too. Huh?
Look, it's 525.
Oh my god, my teriyaki
mayo pizza and gingerbread!
Why don't you just
contact the Game Master?
Yeah, I did that, but nothing's happening.
He's not picking up.
Do you know if there's another
way to log out of this thing?
No, whenever a player
wants to log out of SAO,
the only way they can do it
is by going through the menu.
That can't be right.
There's got to be some other way out.
Return! Log out! Escape!
Told you so.
And there was no emergency
logout in the manual either.
No way. You're kidding. I know.
I'll just rip the nerve gear
off my head. Don't bother.
Once you're hooked in, you can't move
your body in the real world anymore.
The nerve gear intercepts all
the commands you give from
inside the game using an
interface built into the rig.
Seriously?
So now we gotta wait until someone
gets around to fixing the bug?
That.
Or until someone in the real world comes
along and takes the nerve gear off us.
That's it.
I live alone. You?
I got a mom and a sister,
and I'm pretty sure they'll notice
by dinnertime and come look at me.
You got a sister? How old's she?
What's she like?
She's into sports and hates games,
and she's totally not your type, man.
She wouldn't date a gamer
if he's the last guy.
Who cares?
I want to go!
All right, getting kicked
in the balls doesn't hurt.
Get serious.
Don't you think this is weird?
Yeah, totally.
But it's just a bug.
This isn't just a bug.
If we can't log out, it's going to cause
some serious problems for the game.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
I wonder if the developers
even know what's happening.
Because they could just shut down
the server and log everyone out.
But why haven't they made an announcement?
Do you know what's going on?
Uh-uh, someone forced to teleport.
What's going on with you? Huh?
Look, up there.
Now what?
What the hell is that thing?
Is that the game master?
Why doesn't he have a face?
Is this an event?
I'm scared. Don't worry.
It's just part of the opening ceremony.
Attention, players.
I welcome you to my world.
What's he mean by that?
My name is Akihiko Kayaba, and as of this
moment, I am in control of this world.
Seriously?
Is that really you?
I'm sure most of you have already noticed
an item missing from your main menus.
the logout button.
Let me assure you, this is
not a defect in the game.
I repeat, this is not a defect.
This is how Sword Art
Online was designed to be.
He's kidding, right?
You cannot log yourselves out of SAO?
and no one from the outside
will be able to shut down.
or remove the nerve gear from your head.
If anyone attempts to do so,
a transmitter inside the nerve gear
will discharge a microwave signal?
into your skull, destroying your
brain, and ending your life.
What are you talking about?
Come on, that's such BS.
Let's get out of here.
Hey, I can't get out.
Are you listening to this crap?
He's got to be nuts, right?
Right, Kirito? He's not.
The transmitter signals in the
headgear work just like microwaves.
If the safety's disabled,
it could fry your brain.
Couldn't someone cut the power, or...
That won't work.
The Nervegear's got an internal battery.
This is crazy.
It's totally crazy.
Despite my warning,
the families and friends of some of the
players have attempted
removing the Nervegear.
An unfortunate decision, to say the least.
As a result, the game now has 213
less players than when it began.
They've been deleted from both
Aincrad and the real world.
213?
No way.
I don't believe it!
As you can see,
international media outlets have
round-the-clock coverage of everything,
including the deaths.
At this point,
it's safe to assume the likelihood of a
Nervegear being removed is minimal at best.
I hope this brings you a little
comfort as you try to clear the game.
It's important you remember the following.
There is no longer any way to
revive someone within the game.
If your HP drops to zero, your avatar
will be deleted from the system forever,
and the nerve gear will
simultaneously destroy your brain.
There's only one way for
a player to escape now
you must clear the game
right now you're gathered
on floor one the lowest
level of aincrad if you
can get through the dungeon
and defeat the boss?
You may advance to the next floor,
defeat the boss on floor 100, and
you will clear the game. Clear?
What's he talking about?
Why should we believe any
of the crap you're saying?
We can't clear all hundred floors.
That's freaking impossible.
Even the beta testers
never made it that high!
Last but not least,
I've placed a little present in
the item storage of every player.
Please, have a look.
A mirror?
Coin!
You okay, Kirito? Yeah.
Wait, who are you? Who are you?
I'm me. Who are you?
You're not 17!
Wait a second.
Is that you calling?
Kirito?
But how?
The scan.
There's a high-density signal
device inside the nerve gear rig.
It can see what my face looks like.
But how's it know my height and body type?
When you first put the
nerve gear on it had to
do this calibration thing
it asked you to touch
your body all over like
this remember oh yeah
you're right that's where
it got our physical data
but this is what's the
point why would anyone
do this to us i think
he's about to tell us
right now you're probably
wondering why why would
akihiko kayaba developer
of sword art online and
Nervegear do this.
Ultimately, my goal was a simple one.
The reason I created Sword Art Online was
to control the fate of
a world of my design.
As you can see, I have achieved my goal.
This marks the end of the tutorial and
the official launch of Sword Art Online.
Players, I wish you the best of luck.
It's not a game.
It's real.
Akihiko Kayaba created a virtual world.
He designed the NerveGear rig.
The man's a genius.
I've been a fan of his for
a long time, so I know.
Everything he just said is the truth.
If I die in the game,
I'll die in real life!
My God!
Let me out!
Let me out of here!
I can't stay here!
I have a meeting after this!
You're crazy!
Stop pushing!
You have to let us go!
Wait, seriously?
What did we ever do to you?
We just wanted to play a game!
Come back!
Come on, Klein.
Okay, listen.
I'm heading out right
now for the next village.
I want you to come. Huh?
If what he said is
true, and I think it is,
the only way we're
going to survive in here
is by making ourselves
as strong as possible.
In an MMORPG, the money
you can earn, the XP,
once the game starts up, there's only
so much of that stuff to go around.
Look, the fields around the Town of
Beginnings are going to be hunted clean soon.
If we head to the next village now,
we'll have an easier time
collecting cash and points.
Don't worry, I know all the
paths and places we should avoid.
Even if I'm level one,
I can get there easy.
Thanks, but you know those friends
of mine I was telling you about?
We stood in line for a whole
night to buy this, and...
They're back at the plaza somewhere.
And then I can't leave him.
If it were just Klein, but two
more, or even one more... Sorry.
Can't ask a guy I just met to risk his
life for a bunch of strangers, can't I?
So don't worry about me.
Get your ass to the next village.
I'll be fine.
The last game I played, I ran a
guild, so I'm more than prepared.
And with all the stuff you
taught me, I'll get by, no sweat.
Okay.
If that's what you want, I'll get going.
But if you're in a jam,
message me, okay? Sure.
I'll be seeing you, Klein.
Take care.
Kirito!
I...
Hey! Kirito.
Uh, you look better like this.
Way cooler than your avatar.
Yeah, and I think that scruffy face
fits you ten times better, too.
I've got this!
I can do this!
This world can't beat me!
I will survive!
I can't remember the time it is.
It's a very strange thing.
You'd know that I've seen it.
My only hope for me.
I can't know it!
I can't be afraid!
I'm scared.
I want to always do it.
I'm giving everything I have.
Next time,?
beat her.